{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-terms-of-use-js","path":"/terms-of-use","result":{"data":{"wpgraphql":{"page":{"id":"cGFnZToyNDEx","title":"Terms of Use","date":"2020-11-09T22:23:43","content":"<h1>Terms of Use</h1>\n","featuredImage":null,"terms":{"fieldGroupName":"terms","terms":[{"answer":"Please review the following terms and conditions that govern your use of our Web site. Please note that your\r\nuse of our Web site constitutes your agreement to follow and be bound by the privacy statement, legal notices and terms of use (collectively, the \"Terms\").","question":"Welcome to the Web site of EnerBank USA (\"EnerBank\")","fieldGroupName":"terms"},{"answer":"Unless otherwise noted, all text, images, graphics, photographs, video clips, designs, icons, sounds, information, data and other materials (the \"content\") on EnerBank's Web site are copyrights, trademarks, service\r\nmarks or other intellectual property or proprietary rights owned or licensed by EnerBank. You may use the\r\ncontent only for limited, internal, noncommercial, informational purposes. You may print out a single copy of\r\nthe content solely for those purposes, if the copy bears all copyright, trademark, service mark and other intellectual property and proprietary notices displayed on the web page. You may not distribute, publish, transmit,\r\nmodify, create derivative works from, or in any way exploit, any of the content, in whole or in part, for any purpose. Except as authorized in this paragraph, you are not being granted a license under any copyright, trademark, service mark, patent or other intellectual property or proprietary right in the content. Unless otherwise\r\nspecifically indicated, under no circumstances will you obtain any rights in the products, services, processes\r\nor technology described in the content. All of those rights are retained by EnerBank.","question":"How You May Use the Content on Our Web Site","fieldGroupName":"terms"},{"answer":"References that we make to names, marks, products or services of third parties or hypertext links to\r\nthird-party Web sites or information do not constitute or imply our endorsement, sponsorship or recommendation of the third party. Unless otherwise indicated, we do not monitor or control the content of any Web\r\nsites linked to or from our Web site, and therefore we are not responsible for the content of any Web sites\r\nlinked to our site or the terms of use or privacy practices employed by those other sites. Content on EnerBank's Web site may include technical inaccuracies or typographical errors, and we are not responsible for\r\nany reliance you may place on the content. EnerBank may make changes to the content and the products,\r\nservices and programs described in the content at any time without notice.","question":"Links to Other Web Sites and References to Other Companies","fieldGroupName":"terms"},{"answer":"EnerBank does not guarantee that all browsers will correctly display this site. EnerBank continually reviews new technology and supports the industry best practices and most popular browsers; accordingly, this web site may be modified to reflect updates.","question":"Browsers","fieldGroupName":"terms"},{"answer":"<p>While EnerBank uses reasonable efforts to include accurate and up-to-date information on this Web site,\r\nother than as required under applicable law or regulation, EnerBank makes no representations or warranties\r\nabout the accuracy of the information. EnerBank assumes no liability or responsibility for any errors or omission in the content of the Web site. Changes may be periodically made to the information at any time, without notice.</p>\r\n<p>THIS WEB SITE AND ALL CONTENT ARE PROVIDED \"AS IS,\" WITHOUT ANY WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND.\r\nENERBANK HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS, STATUTORY OR IMPLIED, RELATING TO THE\r\nWEBSITE OR THE CONTENT, INCLUDING ANY IMPLIED WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A\r\nPARTICULAR PURPOSE OR NON-INFRINGEMENT, AS WELL AS ANY WARRANTY OF QUALITY, FUNCTIONALITY, ACCURACY, CURRENCY, COMPLETENESS, RELIABILITY, OPERABILITY, USE PERFORMANCE, SECURITY\r\nOR ABSENCE OF VIRUSES. YOU ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY AND RISK OF LOSS RESULTING FROM THE\r\nUSE OF OUR WEBSITE. Some jurisdictions may not allow for exclusion of implied warranties so some of\r\nthese exclusions may not apply to you.</p>\r\n<p>IN NO EVENT SHALL ENERBANK OR ITS SUBSIDIARIES OR AFFILIATES BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES\r\nWHATSOEVER, IN CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING SPECIAL, INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL,\r\nINCIDENTAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES OR DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, REVENUE, USE OR DATA\r\nARISING OUT OF USE OF OR CONNECTED WITH THE ENERBANK WEB SITE OR THE USE OR RELIANCE\r\nUPON INFORMATION CONTAINED IN OR ACCESSED FROM THE WEB SITE EVEN IF ENERBANK HAS BEEN\r\nADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF THOSE DAMAGES.</p>","question":"Content and Liability Disclaimer","fieldGroupName":"terms"},{"answer":"EnerBank's name and logo, and all related product and service names, design marks or slogans are the trademarks or service marks of EnerBank. You are not authorized to use any EnerBank name or mark in any advertising, publicity or in any other commercial manner without the prior written consent of EnerBank.","question":"Trademarks","fieldGroupName":"terms"},{"answer":"Please review our Privacy statement, which also govern your use of this Web site.","question":"Privacy","fieldGroupName":"terms"},{"answer":"Your access to and use of this Web site is subject to all applicable international, federal, state and\r\nlocal laws and regulations.","question":"Compliance with Laws","fieldGroupName":"terms"},{"answer":"We may supplement these Terms at any time. You may want to visit this web page periodically to determine\r\nthe current Terms to which you are bound.","question":"Modification","fieldGroupName":"terms"},{"answer":"These Terms shall be governed by the laws of the State of Utah, without regard to its conflicts\r\nof law principles.","question":"Applicable Law","fieldGroupName":"terms"},{"answer":"<p>We do not share California resident personal information with affiliates or third parties for the affiliates' or\r\nthird parties' direct marketing purposes. California residents also have specific privacy rights provided by the\r\nCalifornia Consumer Privacy Act, as it may be amended from time to time. These include: (1) the right to request information from us regarding what categories of personal data we have collected about you; (2) the\r\nright to request a copy of the specific personal information collected about you during the last 12 months;\r\n(3) a limited right to have such information deleted (with exceptions); (4) the right to request that your personal information not be sold to third parties, if applicable; and (5) the right not to be discriminated against\r\nbecause you exercise your rights. To exercise these rights or to inquire about privacy protection at EnerBank\r\nUSA, you may visit our CCPA Page or contact us by phone at 1-888-390-1220.</p>\r\n<p>Revised 01/01/2020</p>","question":"California Residents","fieldGroupName":"terms"}]}}}},"pageContext":{"slug":"terms-of-use","databaseId":2411}}}